{
    "id": "d91a759a4535480ab63e11362a845993",
    "title": "Errors in the use of relative pronouns",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "83cf4ccfe84945d9885495d0bf91bf85",
            "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Jack, ................................. is my friend, is a good boy.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "whom",
                        "that"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Last year we visited Shimla ........................................ is perhaps the best hill station in India.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "This is the house .................................... I purchased from Peter.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "which",
                        "whom"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We bought some grapes from ................................... we extracted juice.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "whose",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He lent me a mattress on ................................. I slept soundly.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "which",
                        "what"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I have a friend .................................... mother works at a bank.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "whose",
                        "who's"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "With ...................................... were you exchanging pleasantries?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "who",
                        "what",
                        "whom"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "We met a traveler .................................... bag was stolen.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "whom",
                        "whose",
                        "who's"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Air, ..................................... is present everywhere, is essential for the existence of life.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "what",
                        "whom",
                        "which"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Please try to understand ................................... I say.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "which",
                        "that",
                        "what"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}